Finding Aid for the Walter E. Bennett Photographic Collection LSC.0686
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Loose negatives, 1953-1982; 0.5 box.
  - Nader, Ralph., ca. 1970.; Black and white portraits of Nader. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - New York Knicks., ca. 1965. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Black and white action shots of basketball game.
  - Nixon, Richard., ca.1953 -1974. (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Black and white and color shots of Nixon throughout political career. Includes 2.5 x 2.5" and 4 x 5" negatives as well as 35 mm positives. Includes shots speaking, at inauguration, with family, and meeting dignitaries.
    - President Richard Nixon waves to crowd while accepting an award with First Lady Patricia Nixon, daughters Tricia and Julie, and unidentified man ca. 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Vice President Richard Nixon playing the piano for Julie, Tricia, and Pat Nixon (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Pope John Paul II., ca. 1978. (Box 6, Folder 36)
    2.5 x 2.5" color portrait.
  - Ray, James Earl., 1977 June. (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Black and white shots of Martin Luther King assassin and attorney at House Select Committee on Assassinations.
  - Reagan, Ronald., ca. 1980-1982. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Black and white and color shots of Regan during presidency. Includes 2.5 x 2.5" negatives. Includes shots speaking and with former presidents.
    - President Ronald Reagan answering questions during press conference. ca. 1982 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Stepovich, Mike., 1958 July. (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Black and white shots of the Alaskan politician at dinner party.
  - Teotihuacan., 1963 September. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    4 x 5" black and white shot of pyramid.
  - Truman, Harry S., ca. 1952-1953. (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Black and white and color shots of the President speaking and greeting guests.
  - Unidentified., ca.1952-1982. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Various sizes. Black and white and color shots of unidentified subjects.
- Series 5: Batched negatives, 1953-1967; 3 boxes.
  This series consists of negatives by Walter E. Bennett that were organized and batched at Time into subject-specific envelopes. Negatives include: Presidents Truman through Reagan, various politicians, and foreign dignitaries. The original envelopes and subject labels were retained during processing. Folder descriptions were transcribed from original envelopes. Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - Acarto, Anthony "Tony"., 1958 July. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Acheson, Dean., 1957 February. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Governor Sherman., 1956 January 7. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Includes shots with wife.
  - Adenauer, Konrad., 1956 July 13. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Includes shots with Secretary Dulles and Major General Heaton calling on Eisenhower at hospital.
  - Air Force Command Post at Pentagon., 1963 April. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Includes shots of Col. Dorrie E. Jones and Lt. Col. Elmer Torgesen.
  - 82nd Airborne., 1954 July 13. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Shots of division at Fort Bragg.
  - Albert, Representative Carl., 1966 August. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    D-Oklahoma House Majority Leader.
  - Artamonov, Capt. Nikolai Federovich (Hussian Defector)., 1960 October. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Includes shots with Rep. Francis Walter of Pennsylvania.
  - Baker, Bobby., 1960 May. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Baker was an aide to Lyndon Johnson.
  - Ball, George W., 1961 July. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Banda, Dr. Hastings., 1960 May. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Of Nyasaland.
  - Baruch, Bernard., [2 folders].
    - Shots of testimony before Senate Banking Committee., 1955 April 3. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Shots of testimony before Senate Committee on Finance., 1958 April. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Benson, Ezra., 1957 December. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bliss, Ray., 1967 April. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Biographical/Historical note
    Republican National Chairman.
  - Bourguiba, Habib., 1956 November 27. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Of Tunisia.
  - Boyle, William A. (Tony)., 1966 February. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bradlee, Benjamin., 1961 February. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Of Newsweek.
  - Brando, Marlon., 1963 April. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Brinkley, David., 1961 November 15. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bundy, McGeorge., [2 folders].
    Assistant for National Security Affairs.
    - ., 1961 March (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - ., 1962 November (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Bundy, William., 1963 November. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Assistant Secretary of Defense for International Affairs.
  - Bunker, Ellsworth., 1965 May. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Byrd, Richard., 1956 April 6. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Shots of the Admiral at Pentagon press conference.
  - Byrd, Charlie., 1959 September. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Byrd, Harry., 1962 July. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Cain, James M., 1962 April. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Califano, Joseph., [2 folders].
    White House aide.
    - ., 1965 September (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - ., 1967 June (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Caniff, Milton., 1957 March. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Shots of the cartoonist being honored at Bolling Air Base.
  - Cannon, Clarence., 1955 May 25. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    House Representative.
  - Capp, Al., 1957 February. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Cartoonist.
  - Carson, Rachel., 1962 October. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Carter, Douglas., 1967 June. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Castro, Fidel., 1959 May. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Christian, George., 1967 January. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Churchill, Randolph., 1957 April. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Mark., 1954 August 25. (Box 7, Folder 39)
    General.
  - Clark, Ramsey., 1967 March. (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Appointed U.S. Attorney General by Lyndon Johnson.
  - Clifton, Taylor and Bundy., 1961 July. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Connally, Tom., 1954 May 28. (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Senator.
  - Cooper, John Sherman., 1967 May. (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Shots of the Senator (R- Kentucky) in his office.
  - Corcoran, Tommy., 1960 July. (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Washington D.C. attorney.
  - Cronkite, Walter., 1960 August. (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Shots of Cronkite at GOP convention with Edward Murrow, Sen. Everett Dirksen, and Dwight and Mamie Eisenhower.
  - Crossfield, Scott., 1957 November. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Dies, Martin., 1954 August 26. (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Diem, Ngo Dinh., 1957 May. (Box 7, Folder 48)
    President of South Vietnam.
  - Dirksen, Everett., [3 folders].
    - ., 1954 January 16 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - ., 1962 April (Box 7, Folder 50)
      Includes shots with Sen. Bourke Hickenlooper.
    - ., 1962 April (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Dufex, George J., 1956 December. (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Rear Admiral.
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing., 1966 July. (Box 7, Folder 53)
    Professor of Government at Georgetown University.
  - Dulles, John Foster., [6 folders].
    - ., 1954 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - ., 1954 November 5 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      Includes shots with Konrad Adenauer.
    - ., 1955 January 12 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      Includes shots with Canadians: C.D. Howe, Lester Pearson Harris.
    - ., 1957 November (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - ., 1958 May (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - ., 1958 August (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Dun, Bishop Angus., 1962 April. (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Eaton, Cyrus., 1958 November. (Box 7, Folder 61)
    At National Press Club.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., [7 folders].
    - President greeting foreign students., 1954 August 13. (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Shots of Eisenhower practicing golf shots behind the White House., 1955 June 2. (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Shots of Eisenhower returning to Washington D.C. after illness., 1955 November 19. (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Shots of Eisenhower at press conference., 1956 February 25. (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Shots of Eisenhower at press conference., 1957 July. (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Shots with brother Milton., 1958 September. (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - ., 1959 April (Box 7, Folder 68)
      Includes shots with Harold McMillan.
  - Eisenhower, Mamie., [2 folders].
    - Shots of Eisenhower at a birthday party., 1956 April 7. (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - At christening of a jet airliner., 1958 November. (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Elizabeth II, Queen, consort of Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 1926-present, 1954 November 11. (Box 7, Folder 71)
    Shots of the Queen Mother at the White House.
  - Elizabeth II, Queen., 1957 November. (Box 7, Folder 72)
    Includes shots of Queen with Prince Phillip at Washington D.C. press reception.
  - Evans, Rowland, Jr., 1961 February. (Box 7, Folder 73)
    Of the New York Herald Tribune.
  - Evins, Joe L., 1955 June 26. (Box 7, Folder 74)
    Congressman of Tennessee.
  - Ford, Gerald Jr., 1959 April. (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Fortas, Abe., 1958 December. (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Fowler, Henry., 1967 June. (Box 7, Folder 77)
    U.S. Treasury Secretary in his Washington D.C. office.
  - Frankfurter, Felix., 1962 March 30. (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Fuertes, Miguel Ydigoras., 1958 March. (Box 7, Folder 79)
    Shots of the President of Guatemala with Eisenhower, Dulles, and Nixon.
  - Fulbright, Senator J. William., 1961 October. (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Galbraith, J. Kenneth., 1961 March. (Box 7, Folder 81)
    Economist.
  - Gardner, John W., [4 folders].
    Secretary of Health Education, and Welfare.
    - ., 1965 September (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - ., 1967 January (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Secretary of Health Education, and Welfare, riding from office to White House., 1967 January. (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Secretary of Health Education, and Welfare, walking around Jefferson Memorial with daughter and granddaughter., 1967 January. (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - George, Walter., 1954 February 28. (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Goldberg, Arthur., [2 folders].
    Secretary of Labor.
    - ., 1961 September (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Goldberg, Arthur and family., 1961 September. (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Goodwin, Richard., 1961 July. (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Graham, Billy., 1956 April 6. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    Shots of the evangelist with Senators Daniel and Carlson.
  - Gromyko, Andrei., 1961 April. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    Shots of the Soviet Foreign Minister with Mikhail Menshikov, the Soviet Ambassador to the U.S.
  - Guam Conference., 1967 March. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    Includes shots of Gen. William Westmoreland, Robert Komer, Secretary of State Dean Rusk, and Secretary of Defense Robert McNamara.
  - Guthman, Ed., 1962 February. (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Harlan, Judge John., 1961 July. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    Supreme Court Justice.
  - Harriman, Averill., 1966 November. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    Shots of U.S. Ambassador taken day after his 75th birthday.
  - Hatfield, Mark O., 1967 April. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    Shots of the senator (R- Oregon) in his Washington D.C. office.
  - Hayden, Carl., 1962 February. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    Senator (D-Arizona).
  - Heller, Walter., 1962 June. (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Includes shots of David Bell, Kermit Gordon, and James Tobin.
  - Helms, Richard., 1966 July. (Box 7, Folder 99)
    Director of CIA.
  - Hershey, General Lewis B., 1966 June. (Box 7, Folder 100)
    Shots of the Draft Director's appearance before the House Armed Services Committee hearings on Selective Service System.
  - Herter, Christian., [2 folders].
    Secretary of State.
    - Shots of the Secretary of State at a press conference., 1960 April. (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - ., 1960 June (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp., 1955 July 23. (Box 7, Folder 103)
    Shots of resignation announcement.
  - Hoffa, James., [5 folders].
    - ., 1957 October (Box 7, Folder 104)
      Includes shots with Dave Beck.
    - ., 1960 May (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - ., 1961 February (Box 7, Folder 106)
      Includes shots with Martin F. O'Donoghue, Former Chairman of the Board of Motorists.
    - ., 1961 October (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - ., 1962 May (Box 7, Folder 108)
      Includes shots with Samuel Baron.
  - Hoover, Herbert., 1955 November 19. (Box 7, Folder 109)
    Shots of Hoover at Arlington Cemetery.
  - Hoover, J. Edgar., 1965 September. (Box 7, Folder 110)
    Includes shots with Nicholas Katzenbach as they wait for Lyndon Johnson to speak at Crime Commission.
  - Humphrey, Hubert., [4 folders].
    - ., 1960 January (Box 7, Folder 111)
      Includes shots with family in Chevy Chase, Maryland home.
    - ., 1960 July (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - ., 1964 August (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - ., 1965 September (Box 7, Folder 114)
      Includes shots of Chevy Chase, Maryland home.
  - Hussein, King., 1964 April. (Box 7, Folder 115)
    King of Jordan in Washington D.C. with Lyndon Johnson.
  - Ilah, Amir Abdul., 1957 February. (Box 7, Folder 116)
    Prince of Iraq.
  - Jagan, Cheddi., 1961 October. (Box 7, Folder 117)
    Premiere of British Guiana.
  - Jagan, Cheddi., 1961 October. (Box 7, Folder 118)
    Premiere of British Guiana addressing the National Press Club.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird., 1964 June. (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Johnson, Luci Baines., 1965 June. (Box 7, Folder 120)
    With new sting ray.
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., [14 folders].
    - ., 1956 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - ., 1957 May (Box 7, Folder 122)
      Includes shots with Vice President Richard Nixon.
    - ., 1957 November (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - ., 1958 April (Box 7, Folder 124)
      Includes shots with family in Texas.
    - ., 1959 February (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - ., 1960 February (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - ., 1960 August (Box 7, Folder 127)
      Announcing candidacy for president at Democratic Convention. Includes shots of Rep. Sam Rayburn.
    - ., 1961 March (Box 7, Folder 128)
      Includes shots with Sen. Mike Mansfield.
    - ., 1961 November (Box 7, Folder 129)
      Includes shots of Johnson's house.
    - Shots of Johnson delivering State of the Union Address., 1965 January 4. (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Shots of Johnson at a White House press conference., 1965 February. (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - ., 1965 March (Box 7, Folder 132)
      Includes shots of Maurice Yameogo, Hubert Humphrey, Gus Grissom, and John Young.
    - Shots of Johnson at a press conference., 1965 April. (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - ., 1965 December (Box 7, Folder 134)
      Shots of Johnson at his Texas ranch with: F.P.C. Engineer Stuart F. Brown, C.E.A. Gardner Ackley, F.R.B. Martin W. McChesney, Secretary of Treasury Henry Fowler, Bureau of the Budget Director Charles Schwartz, and F.P.C. Chairman Joseph Swidler.
  - Johnston, Clem D., 1954 May 1. (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Joint Chiefs of Staff., 1962 November. (Box 7, Folder 136)
    Includes shots of Robert McNamara.
  - Katzenbach, Nicholas., [5 folders].
    - Assistant Attorney General., 1962 February. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Attorney General., 1965 March. (Box 8, Folder 2-5)
    - Shots of Katzenbach at his desk at Department of Justice., 1965 August. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Kaunda, Kenneth., 1960 July. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Politician from N. Rhodesia.
  - Kefauver, Estes., 1955 December 27. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Shots of Kefauver announcing candidacy for president.
  - Kennedy, Caroline., 1961 May. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    At play in the White House.
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1965 June. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Senator (D- Massachusetts).
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline., 1963 December. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Shots of Kennedy at new Georgetown home.
  - Kennedy, John F., [11 folders].
    - ., 1961 January (Box 8, Folder 11)
      With Eisenhower, Robert McNamara, Thomas Gates, Dean Rusk, Christian Herter, Robert Anderson, Douglas C. Dillon, Gen. Wilton B. Persons, and Clark Clifford at 2nd transition meeting.
    - Shots of Kennedy at 1st press conference., 1961 February. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Secretary of Labor Arthur Goldberg., 1961 March. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Secretary of State Dean Rusk and Ambassador Tommy Thompson., 1961 March. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Shots of Kennedy at a press conference., 1961 April. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Konrad Adenauer., 1961 April. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Berlin Mayor Willy Brandt., 1961 April. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Shots of Kennedy at Fort Bragg., 1961 October 14. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Anthony Celebrezze., 1962 July. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Harold Wilson at White House., 1963 April 2. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Shots of gravesite at Arlington with Children's' graves., 1963 December. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kennedy, Robert., [4 folders].
    - Shots of Kennedy with Sen. John McClellan., 1957 April. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - ., 1960 December (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Aide John Seigenthaler., 1961 June. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Shots of Kennedy with Gen. Maxwell Taylor, Admiral Arleigh Burke, and C.I.A. Director Allen Dulles., 1961 July. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - King, Martin Luther., 1957 January. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Kozlov, Frol., 1959 July. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Laird, Melvin., [3 folders].
    Representative (R- Wisconsin).
    - ., 1962 April (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - ., 1962 June (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - ., 1965 February (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Layne, Bobby., [2 folders].
    - Shots of the Detroit Lions quarterback playing against the Baltimore Colts., 1954 December. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Shots of the Detroit Lions quarterback playing against the San Francisco 49'ers., 1955 December. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - LeMay, Curtis., 1961 June. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Lincoln, Abraham., 1964. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Shots of a framed photographic print of Lincoln.
  - Linowitz, Sol., 1966. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Long, Russell., [3 folders].
    - ., 1954 January 3 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - ., 1957 July (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - ., 1965 July (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Louis, Joe., 1960 June. (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Former heavyweight boxing champion.
  - Luce, Clare Booth., [2 folders].
    - Shots of Luce at White House., 1956 February 8. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - ., 1959 May (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Luce, Henry., 1960 May. (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Macmillan, Harold., [4 folders].
    - ., 1957 April (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - ., 1957 November (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - ., 1957 November (Box 8, Folder 45)
      Includes shots with Eisenhower.
    - Shots of Macmillan's visit to the U.S., 1957 November. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Magnuson, Warren. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Mansfield, Mike., [2 folders].
    - ., 1954 April 23 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Shots of senator with Sen. Everett Dirksen, and Sen. Hubert Humphrey., 1964 March. (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Marshall, Thurgood., [3 folders].
    - ., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - ., 1965 October (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Shots of the U.S. Solicitor General in his Washington D.C. office., 1966 November. (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Martin, Joe., 1954 August 6. (Box 8, Folder 53)
    Includes shots with Snygham Rhee and Nixon.
  - Martin, William McChesney., [2 folders].
    - ., 1961 March (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - ., 1961 April (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - McCarthy, Joseph., 1954 April 29. (Box 8, Folder 56)
    Shots of the Senator and other at Army Hearings.
  - McClellan, John., [2 folders].
    - ., 1955 July 8 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Shots of the McClellan Committee Crime Hearings with Joseph Valachi and James McShane., 1963 September. (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - McCone, John., 1961 November. (Box 8, Folder 59)
    Includes shots with Allan Dulles.
  - McCormack, John., [5 folders].
    Representative from Massachusetts.
    - ., 1958 May (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Shots of the Speaker of the House with Carl Albert (D- Oklahoma)., 1962 January. (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - ., 1962 January (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - ., 1963 December (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Shots of the Speaker of the House with Representative Carl Albert (D- Oklahoma)., 1964 July. (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - McGovern, George., [2 folders].
    - ., 1965 March (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Shots of the Senator (D- South Dakota) in his office., 1967 January. (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - McMathias, Charles., 1967 March. (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Shots of the Representative (R- Maryland) in his Washington D.C. office.
  - McNamara, Robert., [5 folders].
    Secretary of Defense.
    - ., 1961 March (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Shots of the Secretary of Defense with the Assistant Secretary of Defense Paul Nitze., 1961 April. (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - ., 1962 June (Box 8, Folder 70)
      Includes shots with Roswell Gilpatric.
    - ., 1965 April (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - ., 1965 July (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Mead, James M., 1954 May 9. (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Meany, George., [2 folders].
    President of the A.F.L.-C.I.O.
    - ., 1954 March 5 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Shots of the President of the A.F.L.-C.I.O. at a news conference in Washington D.C., 1966 August. (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Michaux, Elder Lightfoot Solomon., 1955 October 1. (Box 8, Folder 76)
    Radio evangelist.
  - Mikoyan, Anastas., [3 folders].
    - ., 1959 January (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - ., 1959 February (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - ., 1962 November 30 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      Includes shots with Dean Rusk.
  - Milles Fountain., 1955 July 17. (Box 8, Folder 80)
    Shots of the fountain in Falls Church, Virginia.
  - Mills, Wilbur., [5 folders].
    Representative (D- Arkansas).
    - ., 1962 January (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - ., 1962 June (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - ., 1965 March (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Shots of the Chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee in his Washington D.C. office., 1967 May. (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - ., 1967 August (Box 8, Folder 85)
      Chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee.
  - Monnet, Jean., 1954 April 16. (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Morse, Wayne., [2 folders].
    - Shots of a photographic print of the Senator aged 9 in Madison, Wisconsin., 1955 January 12. (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Shots of the Senator with family on their farm., 1955 January 12. (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Morton, Thurston., 1964 January. (Box 8, Folder 89)
    Shots of the Senator (R- Kentucky) addressing G.O.P.
  - Mount Vernon., 1960 January. (Box 8, Folder 90)
    Shots of George Washington's home.
  - Mountbatten, Lord., 1955 November 5. (Box 8, Folder 91)
    Includes shots with Admiral Radford and Secretary of the Navy Thomas.
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1962 February. (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal., [2 folders].
    - Shots of the Prime Minister of India at a press conference., 1956 December. (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Shots of the Prime Minister of India during U.S. visit., 1957 April. (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Nitze, Paul., [2 folders].
    - ., 1958 November (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - ., 1967 June (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Nixon, Richard., [7 folders].
    - ., 1954 January 15 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - ., 1954 January 16 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      Includes shots with senators at the State of the Union address.
    - ., 1955 October 14 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      Include shots with Sherman Adams, John Eisenhower, and Dr. White as they leave Washington D.C. to visit Dwight Eisenhower in the hospital.
    - ., 1955 October 22 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - ., 1955 October 26 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - ., 1958 April (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Shots of the Vice President at his house., 1959 April. (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Nkrumah, Kwame., [2 folders].
    - ., 1958 August (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - ., 1958 August (Box 8, Folder 105)
      Includes shots with Eisenhower at White House.
  - Nu, U., 1955 July 9. (Box 8, Folder 106)
    Shots of the Prime Minister of Burma at the White House.
  - O'Brien, Larry., [4 folders].
    Kennedy assistant.
    - ., 1961 February (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - ., 1961 March (Box 8, Folder 108)
      Includes shots of the Kennedy assistant with the Democratic National Chairman John Bailey.
    - ., 1961 July (Box 8, Folder 109)
      Includes shots of the Kennedy assistant Kenneth O'Donnell.
    - ., 1965 August (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - O'Donnell, Kenneth., 1964 August. (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Operation Alert., 1955 July 7. (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Oswald, Marina., 1964 February. (Box 8, Folder 113)